pingidentity.com 2016-04-17

# Privacy Policy

Ping Identity Corporation (“Ping Identity,” “we,” “us,” “our”) values privacy, and we want you (“user,” “you”) to have the information you need to make your own decisions about your privacy.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how we collect, use, share, and protect information about you, as well as the choices you may make about how we use this information. This Policy also tells you how we can verify the accuracy of your personal data and how you can request that we delete or update it.

Our Policy applies to:

  1. All individuals who provide personal information, such as customers, business partners, job applicants, employees, retirees, and others;
  2. All locations where we operate and;
  3. All methods of contact, such as the Internet, including through our website, pingidentity.com (“site”), our services, direct mail, telephone and mobile, and other emerging technologies and methods.

Please note that this site contains links to other sites. Unless specifically stated otherwise, the collection and use of your personal information at other sites, linked to pingidentity.com, are not governed by this Policy. In addition, the site is not intended for children under the age of 13, and Ping Identity does not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under the age of 13.

Please read the following to learn more about our Policy before providing us with any information. By accessing the site or providing any information, you agree to our use of that information consistent with the Policy. If you have questions about this Policy, please e-mail us at privacy@pingidentity.com.

### Ping Identity Website and Marketing

#### What Information We Collect

**Automatically Collected Information**

This site will automatically capture information about you. We use cookies and other technologies to collect information about you when you visit our site or use our website-based services. You can accept or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. Below are examples of information we may collect with these technologies:

  * Your browser type and operating system.
  * Web pages you view.
  * Links you click.
  * IP address.

This Policy does not cover the use of cookies by other sites, of which we do not have access or control.

**Information You Provide**

In connection with activities that require sign-in or subscription, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself, including: your name, e-mail address, and login credentials. Providing this information is completely voluntary. Though you will still have access to the site without providing requested information, you may not be able to use certain services or features that require such information to function. In connection with applying for employment or during the course of your employment, you may be asked to provide information about yourself, including: your name, address, date of birth, Social Security number or other government identification number, bank account information to enable direct deposit, and similar information about family members.

**How We Use This Information**

We will only use and share your personal information as described in this Policy. Ping Identity uses the information we collect to provide the products and services you request, in connection with your employment, to tell you about other products and services offered by Ping Identity, and to manage our sites and services. Ping Identity may share the information we collect about you and the information you provide to us to perform the services you requested, register you with our site, enroll you in communications from us at your request, analyze the use of our products and services, make your next visit to the site more personalized, and contact you regarding administrative issues. We will only use and share your personal information as described in this Policy.

We rely on third-party service providers to perform a variety of services on our behalf. In so doing, we may need to share your personal information with them. Please note that we only provide our service providers with the personal information they need to perform their services and we require that they protect this information and not use it for any other purpose.

While Ping Identity will never sell or rent information about you or your use of this site to other companies, we may at times disclose parts of your information to trusted business partners with whom we have a strategic partnership, or our investors. Your information may be transferred to another company in connection with a merger or the sale of a substantial amount or all of the assets of Ping Identity.

In addition, Ping Identity may use or disclose any information available to it, if required to do so by law, or if necessary to conform with the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process served upon us, to protect or defend our legal rights, or to investigate, prevent, or take legal action regarding suspected fraud, threats to physical safety, or other illegal activity.

### Communications From Us

All users may opt-in to receiving periodic e-mail communications from us. If you do not explicitly opt-in and choose to receive information from us, we will not include you on distributions of information related to this site, other than service-related administrative e-mails. You may choose to opt-out from receiving other communications at any time by following the link provided on all e-mail communications with instructions on how to opt-out from communications from us. In addition, you may contact the site directly at [privacy@pingidentity.com](mailto:privacy@pingidentity.com) to request removal of your personal information from our systems.

When it is necessary to do so, we may send you service-related announcements via e-mail. For example, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we may send you e-mail. Generally, you may not opt out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by e-mailing [privacy@pingidentity.com](mailto:privacy@pingidentity.com).

### Correcting and Updating Your Information

We take steps to make sure your personal information is accurately maintained. You may view the personal information you provided to us to make corrections or modify your information at any time. If you wish to view the personal information you have provided to us, change your personal information, cancel your account, or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, you may contact us at [privacy@pingidentity.com](mailto:privacy@pingidentity.com) or 1001 17th Street, Suite 100, Denver, Colorado 80202. We do not charge for this service and will respond to reasonable requests in an appropriate timeframe.

### Customer Service and Recourse

If you have concerns about this Policy, its implementation, or other related inquiries or concerns, please contact us at [privacy@pingidentity.com](mailto:privacy@pingidentity.com). Any improper collection or misuse of information in violation of this Policy or should reported by e-mail to [privacy@pingidentity.com](mailto:privacy@pingidentity.com). Ping Identity takes seriously any reported violations, and will investigate such violations and correct any misinformation with a user’s personal information.

### Ping Provided Services

#### Information Processed on Behalf of our Customers using our Service Offerings

Ping Identity facilitates the transfer of information for its customers in connection with our service offerings. Ping has no direct relationship with the individual users/employees of our customers and the type of information that is handled by Ping’s service is at the sole discretion of our customers. Therefore, such information may include personal information of users/employees.

An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct their query to their employer or service provider. If the employer or service provider requests that Ping Identity remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

Ping Identity will retain any information we process on behalf of our customers for as long as needed to provide services to our customer or as otherwise required by law. Ping Identity will retain and use this information solely as necessary to provide our services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Changes in This Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to change our Policy, we will post the changes to the Policy here and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### Confidentiality and Security of Your Personal Data

Ping Identity will take reasonable measures to secure the personally identifiable information users provide to us.

We have implemented reasonable information security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

All our employees, contractors and data processors who have access to, and are associated with the processing of your personal data, are obligated to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

### Safe Harbor Privacy Statement

Ping Identity is committed to handling personal information that is collected from individuals from Switzerland and European Union member countries and then transferred to the United States in accordance with U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Principles.

Ping Identity complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland.

Ping Identity has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. Ping Identity utilizes the self-assessment approach to ensure our continuing compliance with this Policy. From time to time, Ping Identity verifies that this Policy is accurate and in conformity with Safe Harbor Principles.

Ping Identity is committed to resolving any disputes that may arise through a process of internal investigation and resolution. If there are any disputes that Ping Identity is unable to resolve, Ping Identity will facilitate the resolution of such disputes by submitting them to an independent party.

Within the EEA and Switzerland, any questions, concerns, or comments about this Privacy Policy may be directed to Ping Identity at [privacy@pingidentity.com](mailto:privacy@pingidentity.com). Ping Identity agrees to cooperate and comply with EEA and Switzerland Data Privacy Authorities to investigate and resolve any dispute concerning Safe Harbor issues. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Ping Identity’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

### Contact Us

If you have questions specifically about this Policy, or to legal issues pertaining to the practices of the Site or your use of the Site, please contact us.

### Copyright & Trademark Usage

Entire contents of this Web site Copyright © Ping Identity Corporation. All rights reserved.

Electronic documents published at this site are protected by international copyright laws. Ping Identity®, PingFederate®, PingOne®, PingAccess®, Identiverse™, Next Gen Identity™, PingID™, and/or Ping Identity Corporation products referenced herein are either trademarks, service marks, or registered trademarks of Ping Identity Corporation in the United States and/or internationally. The names of actual companies and products mentioned herein may be the trademarks of their respective owners. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
